= kisskh.lv =
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
2017 PRAGUE
Right now, we are here at the Prague
Harmonie International Competition
finals venue.
Tonight marks the final round of the
competition and features the two
finalists.
Given the outstanding performances
they both delivered in the semifinals,
our attention is focused on tonight's
event.
Let go! Outta my way!
Where are we going now?
Excuse me! Stop, stop, stop!
I want to go to the toilet!
What's wrong with YOU!
I said I want to go to the toilet!
Don't try anything.
Or I'll put a bullet
right between your eyes.
What the hell, man?
Settle down!
Try not to get blood all over the car.
You think you're better than me,
trying to tell me what to do,
is that it??
Ah!
Come here!
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
We will now present a certificate of
commendation to Kang Pi-o for his role
in elevating the prestige of Korea Arts
High School.
Kang Pi-o, if you would,
please come up to the stage.
EPISODE 1
Dude. All this is kinda overkill.
You were better.
This certificate is hereby awarded to
this student for elevating the prestige
of this school by winning the Grand
Prize at the twenty-seventh Lake Erie
International Junior Competition.
YEAR 1, CLASS 8 NAME: KANG PI-O
OCTOBER 17, 2016 KIM U-HYEOK
PRINCIPAL OF KOREA ARTS HIGH
NO MORE SPECIAL TREATMENT
FOR KANG SEUNG-WOON'S GRANDSON
DROP OUT
GET LOST BASTARD GO AWAY BASTARD
Hey, Han-rim! Found him!
Ew…
Hey. Did you throw this in the trash?
You are an obnoxious little shit.
To think the entire school gathered
to put on a show for you just cos
you won first place at the competition…
That's a pretty messed up thing to do.
Hey, are we all just extras to you?
Then again, winning a competition
must be a walk in the park for Kang
Seung-woon's grandson.
Oh, you're laughing?
What's so funny?
Hold on…
you really think I'm the reason
you didn't win?
If you're so bitter about not winning,
you should go practice some more
instead of picking fights.
And stop blaming others.
I swear…
What about you?
You're just trying to prove yourself,
right?
Cos you got family issues you need to
work out?
- Hey!
- Crap.
What do you guys think you're doing?
Ach, what does she want?
Hey. You picking a fight?
- Leave him alone.
- Hey.
Chill the heck out, Jae-in.
And quit letting this cocky D-bag
use you.
Let's go.
Hey, wait up.
Oh!
Hey! Hey, Kang Pi-o!
How many times do I have to tell
you, huh?
Try and be a little humble.
It's not gonna kill ya.
Everyone at school is already INSANELY
jealous of you.
Did you HAVE to toss the certificate?
I mean, couldn't you have at least
thrown it away at home?
Why should I consider other people's
feelings in everything I do?
Wow.
Seriously, dude…
You a sociopath?
Why don't you just get to the point.
Me?
There wasn't one.
Really? Never mind then.
Uh, actually I was thinking… um…
Sorry.
- Find someone else.
- You don't even know what I was gonna say.
You wanted me to be your accompanist.
Oh? How did you know?
Hey, Kang Pi-o~~~~.
Come on, just hear me out for a second,
okay?
Kang Pi-o~~~
You know I wouldn't ask you if I had a
choice.
But none of the others are any good.
There is absolutely no way I can play
with them.
I don't have time.
Oh, Come on, it's not that much.
Just three--
Wait, no, no.
Two times?
Oh, Come on~~~
it'll barely take up any of your time.
Hm? Hey!
I'm literally begging, can't you
do it like just one time?
Huh?
Look, our skill levels are too different.
If we played together, you'd probably
sound worse than you actually are.
- Is that something you really want to do?
- Wow.
Do you even realize how harsh you sound?
But you're right.
Could you please… use your skills
to cover for me just this one time?
No.
- I won't.
- Hey!
Kang Pi-o!
Hello Genius, I'm talking to you!
Yeah.
This is exactly the reason why…
I can't lose you.
How do you pull off Schumann so
beautifully like that?
Pfft…
Kang Pi-o.
Forget the accompaniment.
You and me…
We should just get married.
Seriously…
I never want to stop hearing you play.
Would you just leave me alone?
No, I mean it - Let's get married!
SONGMIN HIGH SCHOOL
Pass! Pass it! Hey!
SLIDE TO OPEN SLIDING DOOR
Where are you going?
- Watch it.
- Hey!
Hey, Choi Jeong-yo, get up right now!
Gather 'round, guys.
Ugh…
We gotta talk.
Your music assessment's coming.
Do you all really not know how to play an
instrument?
- What assessment?
- Nah, we don't.
How many times do I have to tell you?
At least use a triangle or something and
get it done.
Look if that's not gonna work…
A friend of mine called and said they
need people to fill seats for this.
If you go to this,
I'll count it as your assessment.
- How's that?
- Oh, too bad, I don't feel like going.
Why not, huh?
I'm trying real hard to make this easy
for you.
Nobody watches this stuff…
You're making us super uncomfortable.
Um… Why don't you just give up on us?
Choi Jeong-yo!
Here!
I don't wanna go.
Nah.
Hello, Joe Rider
Ha - Shit…
Man, you're freakin' diligent.
You ever miss a day of school?
Ya get into any trouble today?
Maybe I should do something bad and get
expelled.
Like you'd have the guts to.
- Hop on.
- Okay, let's go~~~!
Get cash fast.
DO YOU NEED QUICK CASH?
When it comes to a man…
He should never forget the hard
times he's gone through.
You boys…
When you make it big and are
raking it in…
don't forget about me.
- Thank you, sir.
- Sure.
- Here.
- Thank you, sir!
You punk…
I put a little extra in there… 'kay?
- Here. Work hard.
- Thank you, sir.
- You can all succeed.
- Thank you.
Oh-ho… Jeong-yo…
Eat up, yeah?
You look a bit skinny.
Yeah, that's right.
Tell your dad - to pay me back, 'kay?
I'm so dead broke right now, y' know?
I mean, we're eating jjajangmyeon
every day. Okay?
Jeez.
Ugh… Hello, this is Happy Loan.
Oh.
- Hey, I'm good man.
- Oh, ma'am!
- I mean, Miss!
- Just take it, dumbass.
- I'm giving it to you.
- Yeah.
Shit.
- Oh, dear.
- Now eat.
MUSICAL INSTRUMENT ARCADE
TRADITIONAL MARKET
MUSIC MALL
Ugh…
I told you not to keep bringing me things
LIKE THAT!
If you keep doing it,
You just make it so hard for me
to hate you, kid.
Hey.
Do you feel sorry for me too?
Is that why you keep bringing me this
stupid stuff?
I feel sorry for you…
And sorry for myself.
And for myself too~~~
GRAND PRIZE PIANO, CHOI JEONG-YO
DEMAND FOR PAYMENT OF OVERDUE INTEREST
MUSICAL INSTRUMENT ARCADE
- Hello.
- You're here.
Are you eating enough?
Of course.
Whoo! It's been a while since I've seen
performance like that, that was
incredible!
How the heck is Hyun-soo still such
a good player?
Most people run out of talent by
middle age and just move their fingers
mechanically, without feeling.
And Maestro Kang obviously loved
Hyun-soo's performance, too.
I mean, if he doesn't like a show,
that man won't even shake your
hand before leaving.
If you ask me, a conductor shouldn't
wear his emotions on his sleeve
like that. It only intimidates people.
Is that right?
I suppose so.
Have you found an orchestra… for Pi-o?
Oh, yeah.
We have meetings with Gyeongseong
Philharmonic and Seonghan Philharmonic
early next week.
Don't worry.~~~~
Oh, Pi-o won't have any trouble
finding an orchestra.
While I am happy that you're getting on
Hyun-soo's good side…
if you start neglecting my son cos of it,
I'll terminate our contract.
Oh, come on, don't say that.
There's no way I could.
The entire company is fully invested in
him right now.
Hey,
Jae-in told me you turned her down
when she asked for your help.
I'm sorry.
Nah, it's all right.
It was the right call. To be honest,
I'd rather you spent the time
practicing than accompanying her.
It's more beneficial for me.
Plus, I'm scared your mom will grab me by
the hair.
… Really enjoyable. Honestly.
Performing with you today made
me realize…
What an absolute honor it is…
to share the stage with you.
Oh, not at all, sir. Thank you.
Really.
Oh, you're here.
You're late.
Uh,
Mister Kang said he didn't want
to part ways just yet, so…
I…
enjoyed your performance.
Thanks a lot. Mm.
I heard Hyun-jeong made you an offer.
Yeah, I'll be staying in Korea for
the time being.
I guess you've eaten already.
- Come in and have a drink with us.
- No, thank you.
So you're Pi-o, huh?
Ah…
I've heard a lot about you.
You won first place at Lake Erie?
Wow.
Well, as expected of your grandson.
It seems he inherited your
musical talent.
Save your flattery for someone else.
There's no need to give an untalented
kid false hope. Be selective with your
compliments.
Speaking empty words…
is worse than saying nothing at all.
- Father.
- Go upstairs.
I don't want to ruin my good mood
tonight.
Hyun-soo was right there, how could you
say something so horrible?
You can hate me all that you want.
But did you have to talk like that in
front of the kid?
Just because you devoted your
life to your child, doesn't mean you can
expect the same from me.
But you know he's your family too, he's
your grandson!
- And he's my son!
- Don't get the wrong idea.
The only reason I let you two stay under
my roof…
is because I take pity on the way
you struggle so hard as a mother,
not because I acknowledge him as my
grandson.
Why can't you acknowledge him?
Why?
You expect me to accept him as my
grandson when I don't know who
his father is?
And above all, he doesn't have what it
takes.
Stop wasting your time on that
half-witted boy, and focus on
getting your life together!
Father!
Begin.
Hail, Mary, full of grace, the lord
is with thee.
Blessed art thou amongst women, and
blessed is the fruit of thy womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death.
Amen.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners
now and at the hour of our death.
Amen.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners
now and at the hour of our death.
Amen.
Come in.
I have something to tell you.
Grandfather,
do you really think I don't have what
it takes?
Could it be that you only want to
believe that because you hate me so much?
I have looked up to you since I was
a kid, do you know that?
I practiced day and night because I
wanted to hear a single word of praise
from you.
But no matter how many times I won
first place,
you never even bothered to look at me
once.
If that's just because you hate me
so much--
So what you're saying is…
"Why would I belittle someone
as talented as you because of my personal
feelings?"
Is that it?
What do you think you're doing?
Do you think I care to see you show
off your technique?
That's the best you can do, and you
have the nerve to say you're treated
unfairly?
Your amateur playing reeks of vanity and
has zero musical soul
The people that I despise above all else
in this world…
are those who think they themselves
are great
just because they are able to play
challenging music.
Unfortunately,
you are one of them.
I've never thought of myself that way!
I only ever wanted your approval,
Grandfather. How is that such
a bad thing, huh?
One more chance.
Please give me one more chance.
If you still don't think I'm good enough
after that…
then I'll give up the piano for good.
I have no time to spare for you.
What if I play the Noblesse Concert?
You dumb arrogant brat.
Just cos you won a few competitions,
you think you could play in something
like that?
What if I could?
Will you come watch me play?
Deal.
If you think you can pull it off,
then you should try.
But if my opinion remains unchanged
after your performance…
you will have to take responsibility
for what you said.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Why would you suddenly want to change
instructors?
Don't you know how good it is to be
connected to Professor Seo?
I don't really care who he's
connected to.
I need a real instructor
who can teach me properly.
Oh, How can that…
Connections are important.
In the end, this industry is just a
business.
Besides…
of all people you want Hyun-soo,
is that it?
No matter how talented he is,
he's still just a performer.
I told Grandfather
that I would show him what I can do at
the Noblesse Concert.
If he doesn't approve of me then…
I'll quit playing the piano.
How will Professor Seo…
teach me what I need?
We haven't even talked about this.
Why? Pi-o, you--
Off to school?
Have a good day.
Mm.
You know, Pi-o's a smart kid.
He knows exactly what he needs and takes
the steps to get it.
You're standing on the sidelines,
what does this matter to you?
Why are you being so prickly?
Let's be frank.
Everyone in the music world knows…
Seo's reputation is overblown.
I think…
Pi-o made the right decision for what he
needs.
If Father had just supported him, I would
never have thought of turning to
Professor Seo.
How would you know how it feels to be so
powerless, Mother dearest?
Wow…
You're a really good player.
I mean, I don't see a single flaw
to point out.
Why did you come here?
I don't think you need my help at all.
You can tell the truth.
Be honest. You didn't like my playing did
you?
No, quite the opposite.
Mm…
Professor Seo… has done a fine job…
stick with him.
Why? What did he say?
Professor Seo… has done a fine job… stick
with him.
That's the best you can do, and you
have the nerve to say you're treated
unfairly?
Your amateur playing reeks of vanity and
has zero musical soul
ARTS & MUSIC HALL
Ugh, I'm so sleepy.
Man… I can't listen to this anymore.
- Let's bounce.
- Sure. Okay.
Ugh…
Let's go before Teach shows up, come on.
Okay.
- Hurry.
- Let's go…
Come on, Jeong-yo, let's go.
Nah, you guys go ahead.
PIANO OPEN REPERTOIRE
KANG PI-O (17) KOREA ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
"Kang Pi-o"?
Hey, do you have an extra handkerchief?
Thanks…
So, what's your name then?
Kang Pi-o.
Pi-o, look over here just once, please!
Take a picture with us!
Ooh, they know how impressive you are.
Oh, my, it's Kang Pi-o!
- Look!
- Why are you in such a bad mood?
Mister Kang Pi-o,
the perfectionist.
Come on, what was it this time?
The cadenza was a mess.
THE PART OF A CONCERTO WHERE
NEAR THE END OF A MOVEMENT
It wasn't like I practiced it.
AND THE SOLOIST SHOWCASES
MASTERFUL TECHNIQUE AND IMPROVISATION
Well… I've realized recently…
that trying to be too flashy during
the cadenza
can be a bit tacky.
When you played it low key…
I think it was good… for the orchestra.
It's not always right for the pianist to
just do their own thing.
- Huh? Oh, oh, Pi-o!
- Pi-o!
- Hello, ma'am.
- Get in, kids.
Oh, I left my sheet music in the
green room.
Go get it.
Huh?
I'll go with you.
You to skipped school to come here,
right?
What'll your teacher say?
Well, my future husband…
you're military exemption is on the line.
School can wait.
Let go.
Who's playing?
They're really good.
Huh?
Damn it! Hey. Hey, Kang Pi-o.
Just… Go. See who it is.
Hello, ma'am.
Uh, I have a cold…
KANG PI-O
What are you doing?
How can you look at someone else's
sheet music!?
Oh, uh, sorry.
Uh, I didn't mean to look at it.
Jeez…
Uh, hey…
Um… Do you remember me?
Who are you?
Oh…
Never mind. Sorry.
By the way, your cadenza sounded a bit
dry.
Was that on purpose?
Oh, it's just…
That was…
just the impression I got.
Well… you're entitled to your opinion.
But if you know so much,
Why don't you get up on stage and show us
what you got?
Was that you?
On the piano just now??
Whoa, awesome.
Hey, you, uh… play really well.
What's your school? Seonye?
Deokmyeong?
Huh? Hey,
Hold up! Wait!
Oh? "Songmin"?
That's not an arts school.
Wow.
That makes it even more insane.
Hold on… um,
Can you give me your social or phone
number?
Uh… Well, you see, I play the
- viola, and--
- Oh, just leave me alone.
- Jeez…
- Hey!
By the way, your cadenza sounded a bit
dry.
Was that purpose?
MUSICAL INSTRUMENT STREET
Hey, You gonna play?
Sorry, Ma'am, um…
Instead of playing it without any
emotion…
couldn't you put a little more heart into
it?
I mean, It's like every note
just sounds kinda flat, you know…?
What are you saying?
"You're" criticizing me?
Yeah, I know.~~~
I know I totally suck.
That's why if you don't play well,
we're gonna be…
so screwed~~~.
If you're so dissatisfied, go find
another accompanist.
Huh? No wait, ma'am.
That's not what I meant…
Ma'am?
Wait, Ma'am!
Ugh…
SONGMIN HIGH SCHOOL
Whoa. She's pretty cute.
Wow.
- She's cute.
- She's really cute.
What the?
Shut up. Who are you?
- Oh!
- Come on.
Don't you remember me?
The music hall? We met the other day?
What the hell…
Listen…
I totally fell in love with the way
you play.
And I'm looking for an accompanist
right now.
Could you please accompany me?
- Get lost.
- Wait, what?
You haven't heard me out.
So, uh… I'll pay you a shed load of money.
I said get lost.
Oh, okay, how about this then?
Look, my mother…
runs a classical artist management
agency.
You accompany me…
I'll get you an audition.
From what I can tell, you're genius
level.
Are you just going to let your talent go
to waste like this?
What the hell are you talking about?
You keep that "genius" crap to yourself.
This is some bullshit, I'm out.
A million won!
I don't believe it…
Did you think I'd pay you peanuts?
Of course you didn't.
Normally,
I pay 100,000 won per session,
but you're special, right?
Two hundred thou.
So, if you do five sessions with me…
That's a…
million. Wow!
That sounds like a pretty sweet gig, am I
right?
Oh, you're a cocky little shit.
So?
What's wrong with my teaching?
What's the matter with it?
You think I don't give a damn about
musicality, and I'm just running a
college prep factory?
Just tell me, kid.
Who is it?
You want to switch professors, but you
feel too guilty to leave, so you're just
looking for an excuse, is that it?
No, It's not like that.
Like hell it isn't.
Don't you bullshit me. Huh?
Don't give me… bullshit like that~~~!
I always felt like something
wasn't right,
but you always just told me to copy your
playing style, so that's what I did.
All you've done is make me a carbon copy
of you.
What?
I'm finished.
Get out. Don't show your face to me again.
You…
I'll do whatever it takes to make sure
you never get a foothold in
this industry. Get out.
Get out!
Hey, Choi Jeong-yo.
- Oh, hello.
- Let's go.
- Hello, kids.
- Hello, ma'am.
- Let's go home.
- It's heavy right?
Oh!
You practiced, right?
That one. Play it.
Pay me first.
Wow… So it's like that.
Here.
Half up front. The rest when we're done.
Will that work?
Let's play.
I hope you have a safe trip back.
- Thanks.
- And I hope you'll consider…
my offer.
An evaluator like you…
could really serve the school.
Well, I'll consider it.
I wonder what we'll get this year.
Last year, we had a fair share
of violinists…
What is it?
Who are you?
What school do you go to?
Oh,
he's from another school.
I just brought him in here as my
accompanist.
I see.
Wait…
Hey! Stop!
Hey! Wait! Wait!
Hey!
Let go, man! I just came here to do a
quick gig!
Pay me first.
I'm owed a hundred grand.
Here.
Play what you were playing earlier.
Now, try modulating it.
Okay, let's try a variation.
What's your name young man?
Choi Jeong-yo.
Tell me, Jeong-yo,
where do you take your piano lessons?
- I don't take any.
- What?
I just play the piano at home when
I'm bored, is all.
Look, uh…
How 'bout you enroll here and learn
properly?
Oh…
So that's what this was all about.
Sorry to break it to you, but I'm
not brainless.
What's that supposed to mean?
You're just looking for another
student to milk for money. Well, I don't
have any.
I'm out.
Actually, no.
We're willing to provide full support,
even a place in the dorms,
if you need it.
We have a scholarship program for gifted
students.
You wouldn't have to worry about
tuition or practice fees. All you'd
have to do is play.
And then what'll I do?
How'll I make a living playing the piano?
It's easy for people like you, uh…
You guys have money.
You can afford to be artists, but for
me…?
Man…
I'd starve to death if I did that.
Have a good one.
Wait a minute.
Call me… if you ever change your mind.
Uh… Nah…
From what I've seen…
I don't think you'll need to worry about
starving.
Call me when you're ready.
All right? Hm?
Sure.
Goodbye.
Woah!
Hold on…
Did Director Yoon just offer you a
scholarship?
Wow, no way, no way!
See, dummy~~~!?
I told you ~~~!
You're definitely a genius.
I knew it.
I, like, literally called it, didn't I?
So, what'll you do?
You'll transfer, right?
- No.
- What?
Are you crazy?
You might not know this~~, but everyone's
dying to get into this place.
Dude, get a grip and seriously
think about it, okay?
Chances like this are rare you know.
I said no.
Huh? Well, why not?
Give me a good reason.
I don't know. I just don't want to.
Why do you care?
You in cahoots?
Who the heck was that kid?
He's a bit rough around the edges,
but you can't deny it; he's got a
real gift. Wow,
I don't think I've heard anyone
play quite like that.
Tell me something…
what made you suggest that he
transfer here?
Around seven years ago…
I was judging a competition and heard
this kid play.
And for some reason, his performance
just stuck with me.
Ever since then, I've regretted
letting him slip away.
That kid.
You know what his name was?
It was Choi Jeong-yo.
Hey bro. Help me pick one of these.
I can't decide, man!
Woah, hold on!
Dude, look. I'm trying to pick
between the white ones, or the ones
with a red stripe.
I mean, the whites are cool, right?
KOREA ARTS HIGH SCHOOL DIRECTOR
YOON SEON-JU
How 'bout you enroll here and learn
properly?
Look, uh…
Huh?
Is that you, Dad?
Right. Search the place.
- Is he here?
- No, he's not.
Oh, damn it…
Kid… where did your dad go?
- I don't know.
- Don't know?
You sure?
- Huh?
- Sucks for you…
Oh…
Sorry… let me see.
Hold on. Okay, calm down, I'll be gentle.
Lemme see.
Yeah, this'll do - we can use this.
Kid.
Call your daddy.
Get him to come here.
Okay?
That's it.
Oh, Cheese and rice…
Give me a cigarette.
HYUN, OCTOBER 28, 2016
Kim's on his way over to your place
right now, man.
You need to bail.
Hey. Use that phone!
- Hey!
- Fuck!
- Boss!
- Ack!
Shit…
Whoa, whoa…
- Shit!
- STOP, KID!
- Whoa,!
- Ah, fuck!
Ah! Shucks…
Stop already.
Damn it!
- Oh, man, I'm outta shape.
- Fuck…
Hey you!
- 'Kay…
- What're you doing?
No don't!
Dammit!
- Come on, get him!
- Yeah!
Hurry!
- C'mon!
- Yeah!
Huh?
What are you doing here?
Drink this and dry off before you go.
You don't wanna get sick.
Sir, please,
Can you just give me a straight answer?
What's wrong with me?
Not knowing what's wrong is driving
me insane.
Everyone just tells me I'm good.
But I know that I'm not.
I don't know if they're just dumb, or
they really can't tell.
But YOU know, Mister Do.
Don't you?
I do.
I think there's a problem with your
musicality.
I think, what's wrong with your playing…
is it lacks your own voice.
Right now, your brilliant technique
is cleverly masking the flaws hiding
behind it.
But if you listen closely,
you'll hear it.
You'll hear that your music is
not genuine.
Your technical skill is some of
the best I have seen,
but having perfect "technique" isn't
enough.
You need to make the E- MOTIONS
beyond the sheet music your own.
Your pain, your joy, your despair.
Your emotions…
must hit the audience right in the heart.
Otherwise, you'll never be a true
musician.
I'd like a room, please.
- We don't rent to minors.
- Uh, why not?
Uh… Please ma'am, I have money.
Just for the night.
Go.
Hello?
Hello…
This is Choi Jeong-yo.
I was wondering if I could…
stay at the dorms for a few days?
Look.
Given your situation, why don't
you transfer to our school?
This isn't out of pity or charity,
so don't get the wrong idea.
Honestly,
recruiting smart, talented students to
the school - looks really good for my
record.
And you fit the bill perfectly.
The phone is turned off. After the
beep, you will be connected to
voicemail, and call charges will apply.
VOICE CALLING DAD
CHOI JEONG-YO KOREA ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
Listen up!
We have a new transfer student in class.
Make sure to take good care of him.
Introduce yourself.
Hi, kids.
Hello, ma'am.
Oh.
I haven't seen you before.
- He's a transfer student.
- What's your name?
- Choi Jeong-yo, ma'am.
What's your major?
- Piano.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Oh.
- Same major as you.
- A transfer? - I bet he's good.
Oh, really?
Come on up here.
- She's gonna make him play.
- I know, right?
Ooh…
Play something.
Well? Go on then.
Oh, he's going to play.
Cool
Um…
May I do it another time?
He chickened out.
Oh, come on.
Sit down.
I'm sorry.
Okay… then, let's start…
from page a hundred and thirty
nine of the textbook today.
"Choi Jeong- yo."
How much?
How much did you donate to get in here?
Pianos? How many?
Two? Three?
Why aren't you saying anything?
- Oh…
- Hey.
Keep this shit up and you'll regret it,
- 'kay?
- Eek.
I'm so scared.
Wow, did they pick you up off the
street? Huh?
Hey, it's cos of low-class kids like him
that our school's reputation is
going down the drain.
I mean, this one - doesn't have
the musical talent to be here.
Not to mention, his background.
Move.
- What's that?
- Can you move? I need my book.
I don't want to.
Hey, hey, hey!
What's going on?
Ya little punks.
- This ain't over…
- Get back to your seats.
Tool…
Thanks for earlier.
- For what?
- You stopped them for me.
I wasn't stopping them.
I just wanted to get my book.
Oh, so that's where you sign up
to use the practice room?
Where can I buy snacks?
You're not in the dorms, right?
Why are arts high schools so damn
complicated?
There are so many weird classes,
don't you think?
All right, that's enough.
What is?
I'm not really big on making friends with
anyone.
You're on your own, man.
Hey, do you have an extra handkerchief?
And the grand prize goes to
Choi Jeong-yo!
Congrats!
Are you out of your mind?
Second place? THAT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
FOUR HANDS, TWO SONATAS
Do you seriously not remember me?
Actually,
there's something I haven't told you.
Go study abroad.
Do you really think I'd run off
to go study overseas?!
How about you do a four-hand piece?
You know, Choi Jeong-yo, right?
Let's see. Can't you afford to buy real
sheet music?
- Boom!
- NO DON'T!
- Dammit!
- Why does it have to be with him?
Have you ever heard him play?
I hate jerks who approach music with
an attitude like yours.
I'm afraid Jeong-yo will have to be held
responsible.
So… I'll have to expel him.